Liam Partridge

Clyde, NC 28721 liamjpart@gmail.com +1 828 593 0127

I am 19 years old, I am a full time volunteer, and enrolled in an online school learning software development. I am looking for a part time remote job so I can continue my responsibilities mentioned before. I am a hard worker with experience with both manual labor, and home jobs. I learn quickly, have a good work ethic, and can work both independently, and in a group.

Work Experience

spray foam insulation

FF Adhesive and Insulation - Asheville, NC December 2023 to Present

I work with this company when they're hired to do specific buildings. Though I've only worked with them once, I plan on working with them in the future. I learned very quickly and was tasked with doing it on my own in a very short time. I would spray the ceiling with foam, then come back and spray a fire retardant. I also spent time cleaning and repairing the spray guns.

Generator Technician

Partridge Electric - Waynesville, NC January 2022 to Present

I would communicate with the homeowner about the work being performed. I would then check all of the generator's systems, to insure the whole unit was working properly. I would then do preventive maintenance on the unit, i.e. replacing components like the batter or spark plugs. If there was an issue, I would diagnose the unit, and make the needed repairs.

Zoom operator

Clyde, NC April 2020 to Present

From the start of the pandemic until now, I've helped maintain Zoom for religious meetings multiple times a week. I act as host or co-host for these meetings, I start the meetings, allow people into the meetings, monitor everyone in the meetings, start polls, and open up breakout rooms.

public volunteer work

Jehovah's Witnesses - Haywood, NC July 2018 to Present

I have regularly participated in this volunteer work for many years prior to 2018. And since September of 2022 I have been doing this full time. This work includes going door to door, writing letters and making phone calls. I have had extensive schooling and training for many years on public speaking, talking to stranger, and writing as apart of this volunteer work.

Generator Installer

Partridge Electrical Services - Waynesville, NC January 2017 to Present

I was a general laborer, setting the concrete slab and generator, running conduit and wire, and terminating wires.

Electrician Helper

Partridge Electrical Services - Waynesville, NC January 2017 to Present

I was a general laborer, helping pull wire, hanging boxes, hanging lights, and wiring receptacles.

A/V set up

voluneer - Greenville, SC July 2017 to July 2023

Once a year, I volunteer my time to help set of large video monitors for conventions of Jehovah's Witnesses. This would involve Organizing all the components, assembling an aluminum frame, attaching monitor sections to that frame, then connecting each monitor with cables.

Podcaster

Fifth Left Audio Drama - Waynesville, NC January 2018 to March 2020

Our small team would write, and record, the script and music for an audio drama we were creating. I would help in the initial writing and development stage of the whole story and each episodes, script writing and editing, and writing music scores. we published 2 episodes before the pandemic shut us down.

Education

Certificate in Software Engineering

CourseCareers - Remote January 2024 to Present

Skills

- zoom operator (4 years)
- Google docs (8 years)
- Computer skills (10+ years)
- Generator Repair
- Electrical Experience
- computer hardware (4 years)
- Communication skills
- Editing
- Proofreading
- Typing
- English
- Transcription
- Google Docs
- · Writing skills

- · Word processing
- Customer service
- Search engines
- Analysis skills
- Google Ads
- Keyword research
- Research
- Windows
- · Operating systems
- Door-to-door
- Sales
- Teaching
- Mac OS
- · Software troubleshooting

Certifications and Licenses

Driver's License

May 2022 to April 2030

Additional Information

I can learn anything, I have very good communication skills, I can work alone or in a group. I have a good work ethic, and can fit into any role thats required